[Wade] You do realize this camp
was closed down,
like, twenty years ago?
But I'm pretty sure
the way the story goes,
some woman, she went nuts.
Killed all these counselors.
Blamed them
for her son's drowning.
The place was called
Camp Crystal Lake.
Jason...
...he came back.
My sister, she came camping up
around here with some friends.
She's gone missing.
[Gasps]
She ain't missing. She's dead.
People go missing around here,
they're gone for good.
No! No, no, no!
Argh!
Here it is.
Make yourselves at home.
Mi casa es su casa.
[Bracke] You know
how many thousands of people
disappear every year?
There's no evidence.
No car, no witnesses.
- Alright, you ready?
- Ready. Let's do it.
[Chewie] This is a man's sport.
Nolan!
[Jenna] There's a guy out there
carrying a dead body.
[Woman] They bring trouble.
We just wanna be left alone.
And so does he.
So does who?
Richie, stop fucking around.
[Screams]